Edward R. Murrow Papers MS025
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Books, 1890 -- 1974; MS025.007; 0.55 Linear Feet
  - The Iron Curtain: where freedom's offensive begins., 1963; MS025.007.MR.01187; Overstreet, H. A. (Harry Allen), 1875-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from authors: For Edward R. Murrow. With warm appreciation. Harry Overstreet. Bonaro Overstreet. The date is the copyright date
  - The strange tactics of extremism., 1964; MS025.007.MR.01188; Overstreet, H. A. (Harry Allen), 1875-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The war called peace: Khrushchev's communism., 1961; MS025.007.MR.01189; Overstreet, H. A. (Harry Allen), 1875-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from authors: To Edward R. Murrow. With warm regards and best wishes. Harry Overstreet. Bonaro Overstreet. The date is the copyright date
  - The war called peace: Khrushchev's communism., 1961; MS025.007.MR.01190; Overstreet, H. A. (Harry Allen), 1875-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Tempestuous journey; Lloyd George, his life and times., 1954; MS025.007.MR.01191; Owen, Frank, 1905-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - I protest., 1954; MS025.007.MR.01192; Oxnam, G. Bromley (Garfield Bromley), 1891-1963. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Mr. Edward R. Murrow, whose creative and courageous leadership has been a constant source of inspiration. From, G. Bromley Oxnam. The date is the copyright date
  - The hidden persuaders., 1957; MS025.007.MR.01193; Packard, Vance Oakley, 1914-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The life of John Stuart Mill., 1954; MS025.007.MR.01194; Packe, Michael St. John. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Compulsory medical care and the welfare state, an analysis based on a special study of governmentalized medical care systems on the continent of Europe and in England., 1950; MS025.007.MR.01195; Palyi, Melchior, 1892-1970. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Special ed.
  - Russia., 1949; MS025.007.MR.01196; Pares, Bernard, Sir, 1867-1949. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Rev. ed. A Mentor book.
  - Organizing the Party for victory over reaction. Report delivered at the National Conference of the Communist Party., 1953; MS025.007.MR.01197; Parker, Alex. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The evolution of political thought., 1958; MS025.007.MR.01198; Parkinson, C. Northcote (Cyril Northcote), 1909-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's note inserted at table of contents page.
  - Roaming the mountains with John A. Parris., 1955; MS025.007.MR.01199; Parris, John, 1914-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For a long-lost Far Heel - Ed Murrow - from his old friend of London and New York - John Parris.
  - A courier in New Mexico., 1936; MS025.007.MR.01200; Parsons, Mabel. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Picture and Tesuque Pueblo inscribed on inside of front cover. Author's signature on title page. The date is the copyright date
  - 21 stayed; the story of the American GI's who chose Communist China: who they were and why they stayed., 1955; MS025.007.MR.01201; Pasley, Viriginia, 1905-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Venus: one world nearer paradise?, 1961; MS025.007.MR.01202; Paterson, Arthur Elliott. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: To our friends, Ed. and Janet Murrow. From the author and Harriet - the Patersons. Publisher's notes inserted at front flyleaf. The date is the copyright date
  - Occupied territory., 1941; MS025.007.MR.01203; Peabody, Polly. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The FDR story., 1963; MS025.007.MR.01204; Peare, Catherine Owens. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Student ed.
  - U.S.A.--second-class power?, 1958; MS025.007.MR.01205; Pearson, Drew, 1897-1969. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: To Ed Murrow, who has already portrayed many of the efficiencies reported in this book. Drew Pearson.
  - Food., 1944; MS025.007.MR.01206; Pearson, Frank A. (Frank Ashmore), 1887-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Dizzy; the life & personality of Benjamin Disraeli, Earl of Beaconsfield., 1951; MS025.007.MR.01207; Pearson, Hesketh, 1887-1964. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Two kinds of time., 1950; MS025.007.MR.01208; Peck, Graham, 1914-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The consumer's manifesto., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01209; Pei, Mario, 1901-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's note inserted at back flyleaf. The date is the copyright date
  - The American political process., 1962; MS025.007.MR.01210; Penniman, Howard Rae, 1916-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The American political process., 1962; MS025.007.MR.01211; Penniman, Howard Rae, 1916-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The colonial reckoning; the end of the imperial rule in Africa in the light of British experience., 1962; MS025.007.MR.01212; Perham, Margery Freda, Dame, 1895-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The Roosevelt I knew., 1946; MS025.007.MR.01213; Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Can we end the cold war? A study in American foreign policy., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01214; Perla, Leo. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Sources of our liberties; documentary origins of individual liberties in the United States Constitution and Bill of rights., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01215; Perry, Richard L. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Bookplate for American Bar Foundation 1952 inserted on inside of front cover. The date is the copyright date
  - Left-wing democracy in the English Civil War; a study of the social philosophy of Gerrard Winstanley., 1940; MS025.007.MR.01216; Petegorsky, David W. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Left Book Club ed. Left Book Club leaflets inserted between p.32-33.
  - The Southern temper., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01217; Peters, William, 1921-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's letter and note inserted at front flyleaf.
  - Cuba, island of paradox., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01218; Phillips, R. Hart (Ruby Hart). (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - For more than bread, an autobiographical account of twenty-two years' work with the American Friends Service Committee., 1953; MS025.007.MR.01219; Pickett, Clarence, 1884-1965. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - A Roman Catholic in the White House., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01220; Pike, James A. (James Albert), 1913-1969. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's note inserted at preliminary title page.
  - George C. Marshall: education of a general, 1880-1939., 1963; MS025.007.MR.01221; Pogue, Forrest C. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Postcard from Ed Brooke to ERM, dated 10/7/63 inserted at front flyleaf. Corner of p.374 turned down.
  - George C. Marshall: education of a general, 1880-1939., 1963; MS025.007.MR.01222; Pogue, Forrest C. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Backdrop to tragedy; the struggle for Palestine., 1957; MS025.007.MR.01223; Polk, William Roe, 1929-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Farewell, France! An eye-witness account of her tragedy., 1941; MS025.007.MR.01224; Pollak, Oscar, 1893-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Henry Ponsonby, Queen Victoria's private secretary; his life and letters., 1942; MS025.007.MR.01225; Ponsonby, Arthur Ponsonby, Baron, 1871-1946. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscribed on front flyleaf: Janet Murrow.
  - Verandah; some episodes in the crown colonies: 1867-1889., 1964; MS025.007.MR.01226; Pope-Hennessy, James. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - People of plenty; economic abundance and the American character., 1954; MS025.007.MR.01227; Potter, David Morris. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Charles R. Walgreen Foundation lectures. Annotated. Two pages of hand-written notes inserted at p. vii. Bookmark inserted with 134 inserted between p.134-35. Bookmark inserted between p.176-77.
  - Channels of learning; the story of educational television., 1962; MS025.007.MR.01228; Powell, John Walker, 1904-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The school bus law; a case study in education, religion, and politics., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01229; Powell, Theodore. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Constitutional metaphors: a review of James M. Beck's The Constitution of the United States: originally published in The new republic of February 11, 1925., 1941; MS025.007.MR.01230; Powell, Thomas Reed, 1880-1955. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - A short history of the Civil War: (Ordeal by fire)., 1948; MS025.007.MR.01231; Pratt, Fletcher, 1897-1956. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Collector's ed. The date is the copyright date
  - The happy republic; a reader in Tocqueville's America., 1962; MS025.007.MR.01232; Probst, George E. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Harper torchbooks. The Academy library. TB1060.
  - Estonia; population, cultural and economic life., 1937; MS025.007.MR.01233; Pullerits, Albert. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Envelope with 3 items inserted at front flyleaf: Daniel Whetsone's card with note, compliments card from the Consulate General of Estonia, and CBS typed promotion.
  - Brave men., 1944; MS025.007.MR.01234; Pyle, Ernie, 1900-1945. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Here is your war., 1943; MS025.007.MR.01235; Pyle, Ernie, 1900-1945. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: Janet and Ed Murrow, November, 1944. The date is the copyright date
  - Republican Germany: a political and economic study., 1928; MS025.007.MR.01236; Quigley, Hugh, b. 1895. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Annotated. Inscription on front flyleaf: [Soyez a moivrer?] Berlin, Nov. 1929.
  - Czechoslovakia: under the hammer and sickle. [item pulled in April 2011 and added to Murrow collection folder titled 'Zenkl, Petr' because of preservation concerns., 1953; MS025.007.MR.01237; Rada svobodnho Ceskoslovenska. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    [2d ed.]
  - Portrait of an American labor leader: William L. Hutcheson; saga of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of American, 1881-1954., 1955; MS025.007.MR.01238; Raddock, Maxwell C. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - No compromise: the conflict between two worlds., 1939; MS025.007.MR.01239; Rader, Melvin Miller, 1903-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Mike and screen press directory and newsguide., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01240; Radio-Newsreel-Television Working Press Association. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    5th ed. The date is the copyright date
  - Mike and screen press directory and newsguide., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01241; Radio-Newsreel-Television Working Press Association. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Extraits de l'Histoire de la civilisation francaise., 1927; MS025.007.MR.01242; Rambaud, Alfred, 1842-1905. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Annotated. Inscription on inside cover: Harriet H. Brewster.
  - A foreign economic policy for the United States., 1954; MS025.007.MR.01243; Randall, Clarence B. (Clarence Belden), b. 1891. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Charles R. Walgreen Foundation lectures. Publisher's notes inserted at front flyleaf.
  - The communist challenge to American business., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01244; Randall, Clarence B. (Clarence Belden), b. 1891. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. An Atlantic Monthly Press book. Publisher's note inserted at front flyleaf. The date is the copyright date
  - Central intelligence and national security., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01245; Ransom, Harry Howe, 1922-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Fights, games, and debates., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01246; Rapoport, Anatol, 1911-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Estonia, a reference book., 1953; MS025.007.MR.01247; Raud, Villibald. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The limitist., 1947; MS025.007.MR.01248; Raymond, Fred Ingalls, 1894-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Mr. Edward R. Murrow in the interest of a sound [??] Fred I. Raymond. January 10, 1956. Publisher's leaflet inserted on last page of book. The date is the copyright date
  - The limitist., 1947; MS025.007.MR.01249; Raymond, Fred Ingalls, 1894-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Mr. Edward R. Murrow, from Fred I. Raymond. Sept. 12, 1950. The date is the copyright date
  - Lord Burghley and Queen Elizabeth., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01250; Read, Conyers, 1881-1959. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - To hell with culture; democratic values are new values., 1941; MS025.007.MR.01251; Read, Herbert Edward, Sir, 1893-1968. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    The Democratic Order, no. 4. Inscription on front flyleaf: Janet Murrow. June 1941- Letter to Janet Murrow, dated 6/10/41 from Leslie, The British War Relief Society in Washington D.C., inserted at front flyleaf.
  - A prophet at home., 1941; MS025.007.MR.01252; Reed, Douglas, 1895-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Sequel to Insanity fair and Disgrace abounding.
  - Disgrace abounding., 1939; MS025.007.MR.01253; Reed, Douglas, 1895-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Sequel to Insanity fair. Corner of p.151 turned down.
  - Insanity fair., 1938; MS025.007.MR.01254; Reed, Douglas, 1895-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - American strategy in the atomic age., 1955; MS025.007.MR.01255; Reinhardt, George C. (George Cooper), 1902-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - United States foreign policy, 1945-1955., 1956; MS025.007.MR.01256; Reitzel, William, 1901-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Press release from publisher inserted on last page.
  - The Dutch nation; an historical study., 1944; MS025.007.MR.01257; Renier, Gustaaf Johannes, 1892-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Decisions for a better America., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01258; Republican Committee on Program and Progress (U.S.). (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Prelude to victory., 1942; MS025.007.MR.01259; Reston, James, 1909-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Annotated (last page). Letter from Allan Michie of Reader's digest to Mrs. Benson folded and inserted between p.154-55.
  - Unite or perish; a dynamic program for a united Europe., 1951; MS025.007.MR.01260; Reynaud, Paul, 1878-1966. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - By Quentin Reynolds., 1963; MS025.007.MR.01261; Reynolds, Quentin James, 1902-1965. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Where is wisdom?: Addresses of President Stephen L. Richards., 1955; MS025.007.MR.01262; Richards, Stephen L. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: To 'Ed.' Murrow Esq. from Claude Richards 1960. My hearty congratulations on your distinguished contribution as a broadcaster to the welfare our country. Guard your health, please. CR. Claude Richards' address inscribed on inside of back cover. Biography of Stephen Richards pasted to inside of front cover. The date is the copyright date
  - Education and freedom., 1959; MS025.007.MR.01263; Rickover, Hyman George. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Foreword by Edward R. Murrow. Pref. by Charles Van Doren. 1st ed. Publisher's note inserted at front flyleaf.
  - They were there; the story of World War II and how it came about by America's foremost correspondents., 1944; MS025.007.MR.01264; Riess, Curt, 1902-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on title page: Janet Murrow. The date is the copyright date
  - Red China's fighting hordes, a realistic account of the Chinese Communist army., 1951; MS025.007.MR.01265; Rigg, Robert B. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The dark invader; wartime reminiscences of a German naval intelligence officer., 1933; MS025.007.MR.01266; Rintelen, Franz von. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Stamped: CBS News Special Projects Library.
  - Globe and hemisphere: Latin America's place in the postwar foreign relations of the United States., 1958; MS025.007.MR.01267; Rippy, J. Fred (James Fred), 1892-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Foundation for Foreign Affairs Series, no. 1. Published in cooperation with Foundation for Foreign Affairs, Inc.
  - Stroke: a diary of recovery., 1960; MS025.007.MR.01268; Ritchie, Douglas. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - I saw England., 1941; MS025.007.MR.01269; Robertson, Ben, 1903-1943. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Prospect for America: the Rockefeller panel reports., 1961; MS025.007.MR.01270; Rockefeller Brothers Fund. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Nationalism and culture., 1937; MS025.007.MR.01271; Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Two publisher's pamphlets and fliers inserted at front flyleaf. Publisher's note pasted to front flyleaf. The date is the copyright date
  - Nationalism and culture., 1937; MS025.007.MR.01272; Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Publisher's note pasted to front flyleaf. The date is the copyright date
  - Pioneers of American freedom: origin of liberal and radical thought in America., 1949; MS025.007.MR.01273; Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Rome of the renaissance and to-day., 1932; MS025.007.MR.01274; Rodd, Rennell, 1858-1941. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - Robert Moses, builder for democracy., 1952; MS025.007.MR.01275; Rodgers, Cleveland, b. 1885. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Two photographs of Robert Moses and publisher's notes inserted between p.210-11. The date is the copyright date
  - Confessions of a dealer., 1936; MS025.007.MR.01276; Rohan, Thomas, 1860-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    4th ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: With the authors warm regards, Thomas Rohan [?]. July 1939.
  - World construction: a practical plan through which you can make the world a better place in which to live., 1954; MS025.007.MR.01277; Rollman, Heinz W., 1911-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - I walked with heroes., 1961; MS025.007.MR.01278; Romulo, Carlos P. (Carlos Pea), 1899-1985. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Publisher's notes (biography, leaflets) inserted between p.112-13. The date is the copyright date
  - The meaning of Bandung., 1956; MS025.007.MR.01279; Romulo, Carlos P. (Carlos Pea), 1899-1985. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    The Weil Lectures on American Citizenship. Publisher's note inserted at front flyleaf. The date is the copyright date
  - As he saw it., 1946; MS025.007.MR.01280; Roosevelt, Elliott, 1910-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - America chooses! In the words of President Roosevelt (June 1940-June 1941) with a running commentary., MS025.007.MR.01281; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    presented by Gordon Beckles [pseud.].
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt's own story, told in his own words from his private and public papers., 1951; MS025.007.MR.01282; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Inscription on front flyleaf from editor: To Ed Murrow who reported the news during FDR's most critical period with vigor, accuracy and fairness. Donald Day. Chappaqua, N.Y. Oct. 21, 1951. 127 Hamilton Road.
  - Wartime correspondence between President Roosevelt and Pope Pius XII., 1947; MS025.007.MR.01283; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - A sentimental safari., 1963; MS025.007.MR.01284; Roosevelt, Kermit, 1889-1943. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
  - The autobiography of Theodore Roosevelt. Condensed from the original ed., supplemented by letters, speeches, and other writings., 1958; MS025.007.MR.01285; Roosevelt, Kermit, 1889-1943. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Centennial ed. The date is the copyright date
  - You and your leaders: their actions and your reactions, 1936-1956., 1957; MS025.007.MR.01286; Roper, Elmo Burns, 1900-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf from author: For Ed Murrow,* First in his field! With warmest regards, Elmo. *A profound thinker! The date is the copyright date
  - Pitt., 1891; MS025.007.MR.01287; Rosebery, Archibald Philip Primrose, Earl of, 1847-1929. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    1st ed. Twelve English statesmen. Inscription on front flyleaf: J. Fossman[?]
  - Pitt., 1898; MS025.007.MR.01288; Rosebery, Archibald Philip Primrose, Earl of, 1847-1929. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Twelve English statesmen.
  - Peace through strength; Bernard Baruch and a blueprint for security., 1953; MS025.007.MR.01289; Rosenbloom, Morris Victor, 1915-. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Limited ed. Copy # 653. Inscription on front flyleaf from author: To Edward R. Murrow - With respect and admiration for the clarity, candor and courage so much a part of your reporting - Sincerely, Morris V. Rosenbloom. Jan. 9, 1953. Author's signature on edition statement. Bookmark from author and mailing label inserted between p.104-5.
  - The story of Franklin D. Roosevelt., 1949; MS025.007.MR.01290; Rosenblum, Marcus. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)